Guide to the William C. Bullitt Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Personal and Family Papers, 1840-1998; Series VI
  - Family
    - Bullitt, Anne Moen
      - Correspondence
        - Death of William C. Bullitt, 1967 (Box 214, Folder 273 - 275)
        - Greene, William M., 1978 (Box 214, Folder 276)
        - Mark Paterson and Associates, 1984-1988 (Box 214, Folder 277 - 278)
        - Morkowska, Elizabieta, 1984-1988 (Box 214, Folder 279)
        - Paris apartment, 1967-1974 (Box 214, Folder 280)
        - Researchers [includes bibliography], 1966-1998 (Box 214, Folder 281 - 292)
        - So Close to Greatness, 1974-1987 (Box 215, Folder 293 - 307)
          See also: Oversize Folder 71
        - Sweeney, Conor, undated (Box 215, Folder 308)
        - Yale papers, 1967-1968 (Box 215, Folder 309)
      - Estate of William C. Bullitt, 1967-1994 (Box 215, Folder 310 - 312)
      - Estate of William C. Bullitt, 1967-1994 (Box 216, Folder 313 - 320)
      - Family history research
        - Articles about William C. Bullitt and Louise Bryant, 1940-1991 (Box 216, Folder 321 - 322)
          See also: Oversize Folder 22
        - Notes, undated (Box 216, Folder 323 - 329)
      - Legal, 1924-1987 (Box 217, Folder 330 - 334)
      - Photographs
        - General, undated (Box 217, Folder 335)
          See also: Oversize Folder 59
        - Horse racing, undated (Box 217, Folder 336)
        - Brewster, Daniel [includes negatives], 1942, 1963-1968, undated (Box 217, Folder 337 - 350)
        - Brewster, Daniel [includes negatives], undated (Box 218, Folder 351 - 353)
      - Printed matter
        - Clippings
          - Bryant, Louise, 1982-1983 (Box 218, Folder 354)
          - Obituaries of William C. Bullitt, 1967 (Box 218, Folder 355)
          - Reds, 1979-1982 (Box 218, Folder 356 - 357)
          - Miscellaneous (Box 218, Folder 358 - 359)
        - Miscellaneous (Box 218, Folder 360)
      - Spain trip, 1948 (Box 218, Folder 361 - 364)
        See also: Oversize Folder 72
      - Miscellaneous (Box 218, Folder 365)
- Printed Matter, 1882-1965; Series VII
  This series consists of printed and published material collected by Bullitt, which is arranged by type of material. It includes inscribed books, press clippings, pamphlets, Congressional publications, magazines, maps, and other matter. The most common subjects that the clippings address are Bullitt's support for American intervention in World War II, his warnings about the post-World War II peace settlement and the threat of communism, communism in China, World War I, and his appointment as ambassador to the Soviet Union.
  - Art prints, undated (Box 219, Folder 1)
  - Asian art books, undated
    See: Oversize Folder 24 - 26
  - Books, inscribed
    - Ammirato, Mary Collins. Palm Tree Daughters. [autographed by author], 1938 (Box 219, Folder 2)
    - Atkinson, James David. The Edge of War. [autographed by author], 1960 (Box 219, Folder 3)
    - Barnes, Albert C. Art of Renoir. [autographed by author], 1935 (Box 219, Folder 4)
    - Barnes, Albert C. and Violette de Mazia. The French Primitives and Their Forms. [autographed by author], 1950 (Box 220, Folder 5)
    - Bashkirtseff, Marie. The Journal of a Young Artist. [inscribed], 1919 (Box 220, Folder 6)
    - Biddle, Francis. The World's Best Hope. [autographed by author], 1948 (Box 220, Folder 7)
    - Blum, Leon. L'Histoire Jugera. [autographed by Suzanne Blum], 1943 (Box 221, Folder 8)
    - Blum, Leon. L'Histoire Jugera. [autographed by author], 1945 (Box 221, Folder 9)
    - Bonnet, Georges. Défense de la Paix de Washington au quai D'Orsay. [autographed by author], 1946 (Box 221, Folder 10)
    - Boris, Georges. La Révolution Roosevelt. [autographed by author], 1937 (Box 221, Folder 11)
    - Bullitt, Nora Iasigi. Three Weeks in Russia. [autographed by author], 1936 (Box 221, Folder 12)
    - Bullitt, William C. Le Destin du Monde., 1948 (Box 222, Folder 13)
    - Bullitt, William C. The Great Globe Itself., 1946 (Box 222, Folder 14)
    - Caraco, Albert. Contes Retour de Xerxès. [autographed by author], 1943 (Box 222, Folder 15)
    - Caraco, Albert. Le Mystère d'Eusebe. [inscribed], 1942 (Box 222, Folder 16)
    - Coudenhove-Kalergi, Richard. Die Europäische Nation. [autographed by author], 1953 (Box 222, Folder 17)
    - Croubois, Auguste, et J. Jacquot. Controverses 2e Vaccin Spirituel contre La Rage Guerrière. [inscribed], 1938 (Box 223, Folder 18)
    - Croubois, Auguste, et J. Jacquot. Controverses 2e Vaccin Spirituel contre La Rage Guerrière. [inscribed], 1938 (Box 223, Folder 19)
    - Dickinson, John. Hold Fast the Middle Wa y. [autographed by author], 1935 (Box 223, Folder 20)
    - Edwards, Henry Stillwell. Eneas Africanus. [autographed by Evie and Chip Robert], 1951 (Box 223, Folder 21)
    - Farley, James A. Addresses of the Hon. James A. Farley. [autographed by author], 1934 (Box 223, Folder 22)
    - Farley, James A. Jim Farley's Story. [autographed by author], 1948 (Box 223, Folder 23)
    - Filene, Edward A. Successful Living in this Machine Age. [autographed by author], 1932 (Box 224, Folder 24)
    - Fisher, George J. B. Le Sauvetage du Canal de Panama. [inscribed], 1934 (Box 224, Folder 25)
    - Gachons, Jacques des. Gens de France au Labeur. [autographed by author], 1925 (Box 224, Folder 26)
    - Galsworthy, John. The Pigeon. [autographed by Cole Porter], 1912 (Box 224, Folder 27)
    - Gamelin, Maurice. Servir. [autographed by author], 1946 (Box 224, Folder 28)
    - Gerard, James W. Sketch of Russian History. [autographed by author], undated (Box 224, Folder 29)
    - Gough, John Francis. The Private Letters of Baron de Viomenil on Polish Affairs. [autographed by editor], 1935 (Box 224, Folder 30)
    - Harosin, J. La Palestine et les Etats-Unis Arabes. [autographed by author], 1938 (Box 225, Folder 31)
    - Holmes, Oliver Wendell. Speeches. [autographed by Ferris?], 1943 (Box 225, Folder 32)
    - Hornbeck, Stanley K. "China" and the United States "China Policy." [autographed by author], 1961 (Box 225, Folder 33)
    - Hu Shih. The Chinese Renaissance. [autographed by author], 1934 (Box 225, Folder 34)
    - Ickes, Harold L. Fightin' Oil. [autographed by author], 1943 (Box 225, Folder 35)
    - Ingersoll, R. Sturgis. Henry McCarter. [autographed by author], 1944 (Box 225, Folder 36)
    - L'Armorial Français, 1931 (Box 226, Folder 37)
    - Linebarger, Paul Myro. Mes Mémoires Abrégés sur les Révolutions de Sun Yat-sen. [inscribed], 1938 (Box 226, Folder 38)
    - Lippitt, Marion Almy. I Married a New Englander. [autographed by author], 1947 (Box 226, Folder 39)
    - Lowry, Charles W. Communism and Christ. [autographed by Connie and Tommy White], 1952 (Box 226, Folder 40)
    - Moulton, Harold G. The Control of Germany and Japan. [autographed by author], 1944 (Box 226, Folder 41)
    - Museum of Modern Art. Art in Our Time. [inscribed], 1939 (Box 226, Folder 42)
    - Narodny, Ivan. The Art of Robert Winthrop Chandler. [autographed by author], 1934
      See: Box 245, folder 52a Oversize Box
    - Nixon, Richard M. Six Crises. [autographed by author], 1962 (Box 227, Folder 43)
    - Notovitch, Nicolas. La Russie et L'Alliance Anglaise. [autographed by author], 1906 (Box 227, Folder 44)
    - Reed, John. Ten Days That Shook the World. [autographed by Louise Bryant], 1922 (Box 227, Folder 45)
    - Roosevelt, Franklin D. Addresses of Franklin D. Roosevelt. [autographed by author], 1941 (Box 227, Folder 46)
    - Rostrend, Georges. Franco Means Business. [inscribed], 1937 (Box 228, Folder 47)
    - Shelley, Percy Bysshe. The Great War-Cloud. [autographed by Shirley Carson Jenney], undated (Box 228, Folder 48)
    - Sie Cheou-kang. President Chiang Kai-shek. [autographed by author], 1959 (Box 228, Folder 49)
    - Sinclair, Upton. Between Two Worlds. [autographed by author], 1941 (Box 228, Folder 50)
    - Smythe, David. American Vice-Consul. [autographed by author], 1942 (Box 228, Folder 51)
    - Snow, Edgar. Red Star over China. [inscribed], 1934 (Box 229, Folder 52)
    - Spellman, Francis J. No Greater Love. [autographed by author], 1945 (Box 229, Folder 53)
    - Tabouis, Geneviève. They Called Me Cassandra. [autographed by author], 1942 (Box 229, Folder 54)
    - Thomas, Elbert. Thomas Jefferson. [autographed by author], 1942 (Box 230, Folder 55)
    - Voie de la Liberté. [autographed by Guy de la Vasselais], [1948?] (Box 230, Folder 56)
    - Weigh, Ken Shen. Russo-Chinese Diplomacy. [autographed by author], 1928 (Box 230, Folder 57)
    - Wilde, Oscar. The Soul of Man Under Socialism. ["For Ernesta Drinker from H.A."], 1909 (Box 230, Folder 58)
    - William, Maurice. Sun-Yat-Sen Versus Communism. [autographed by author], 1932 (Box 230, Folder 59)
  - Clippings
    - Bullitt, Aimée Ernesta Drinker, 1915-1916 (Box 231, Folder 60)
    - China, 1948-1949 (Box 231, Folder 61 - 63)
    - Shanghai Evening Post, 1948 (Box 231, Folder 64 - 70)
    - War cartoons, 1939 (Box 231, Folder 71)
    - Yale University, 1911-1912 (Box 231, Folder 72)
    - 1913-1914 (Box 231, Folder 73)
    - 1913-1917 (Box 232, Folder 74 - 77)
    - 1915-1921 (Box 232, Folder 78)
    - 1933 (Box 232, Folder 79)
    - 1933-1934 (Box 232, Folder 80 - 83)
    - 1938 (Box 232, Folder 84)
    - 1939-1940 (Box 232, Folder 85 - 86)
    - 1940 (Box 232, Folder 87)
    - 1940-1941 (Box 232, Folder 88 - 89)
    - 1940-1941 (Box 233, Folder 90 - 93)
    - 1942 (Box 233, Folder 94 - 96)
    - 1943 (Box 233, Folder 97 - 104)
    - 1943 (Box 234, Folder 105 - 115)
    - 1944 (Box 234, Folder 116 - 119)
    - 1945 (Box 234, Folder 120)
    - 1947 (Box 235, Folder 121 - 125)
    - 1948 (Box 235, Folder 126)
    - 1950-1952 (Box 235, Folder 127)
    - 1952-1953 (Box 235, Folder 128)
    - 1953 (Box 235, Folder 129)
    - Unsorted (Box 235, Folder 130 - 135)
    - Unsorted (Box 236, Folder 136 - 156)
  - Congressional publications, 1933, 1940-1942, 1948-1950 (Box 237, Folder 157 - 161)
  - Currency, copies, 1921, 1942, undated (Box 237, Folder 162)
  - Maps and blueprints, undated (Box 237, Folder 163)
    See also: Oversize Folder 8
    See also: Oversize Folder 96
  - Memorabilia (Box 237, Folder 164)
  - Pamphlets
    - Indonesia, 1948 (Box 237, Folder 165 - 166)
    - New York urban planning, 1937-1943 (Box 237, Folder 167 - 168)
      See also: Oversize Folder 53
    - New York urban planning, 1937-1943 (Box 238, Folder 169 - 171)
    - Poland, 1941 (Box 238, Folder 172)
    - Political, 1882, 1917, 1933-1942 (Box 238, Folder 173 - 182)
    - Political, 1943-1952, 1963-1965, undated (Box 239, Folder 183 - 192)
    - Russia, 1921, 1933-1937, 1946-1947, undated (Box 239, Folder 193 - 196)
    - Miscellaneous, 1931-1955, 1963-1964, undated (Box 240, Folder 197 - 206)
      See also: Oversize Folder 54
  - Periodicals
    - The Coffee House, 1933, 1945 (Box 240, Folder 207)
    - Geneva Special Studies, 1933-1934 (Box 240, Folder 208)
    - Liberator, 1918-1921 (Box 240, Folder 209 - 212)
    - Yale University Library Gazette, 1939-1940 (Box 240, Folder 213)
    - Miscellaneous, 1943, 1950-1952 (Box 241, Folder 214)
      See also: Oversize Folder 57
  - Plays, 1917, 1934, 1947 (Box 241, Folder 215 - 216)
  - Postcards, blank, undated (Box 241, Folder 217)
  - Posters, 1944
    See: Oversize Folder 68
  - Miscellaneous (Box 241, Folder 218)
    See also: Oversize Folder 12
    See also: Oversize Folder 69
- Oversize
  - Correspondence, 1948 (Box 242, Folder 1)
  - Cunningham report, 1942 (Box 242, Folder 2)
  - Georgetown University, 1934, 1952 (Box 242, Folder 3)
  - Joint Congressional Committee on Foreign Economic Cooperation (China), financial, 1948 (Box 242, Folder 4)
  - Joint Congressional Committee on Foreign Economic Cooperation (China), Hong Kong, 1948 (Box 242, Folder 5)
  - Journalism research materials, Chinese army nutrition program, undated (Box 242, Folder 6)
  - League of Nations Covenant, president's proposal, no. 2, original, 1919 (Box 242, Folder 7)
  - Maps and blueprints, general, 1925, 1939, 1964, undated (Box 242, Folder 8)
  - Maps, North Africa, 1941 (Box 242, Folder 9)
  - North Africa mission, 1941 (Box 242, Folder 10)
  - Paris Peace Conference administrative materials, 1919 (Box 242, Folder 11)
  - Printed matter, miscellaneous (Box 242, Folder 12)
  - Special Assistant to the Secretary of State, invitations [London Economic Conference], 1933 (Box 242, Folder 13)
  - Speeches, articles, and notes, undated (Box 242, Folder 14)
  - Ambassador-at-large, undated (Box 243, Folder 15)
  - Ambassador to France memorabilia, 1937-1940, undated (Box 243, Folder 16 - 21)
  - Articles about Bullitt, 1934-1943 (Box 243, Folder 22)
  - Articles by Bullitt, 1919, 1944-1950 (Box 243, Folder 23)
  - Asian art books, undated (Box 244, Folder 24 - 26)
  - Banking, 1936-1940 (Box 244, Folder 27 - 31)
  - China data, 1948 (Box 245, Folder 32)
  - China trip arrangements, 1948 (Box 245, Folder 33)
  - Clippings, unsorted (Box 245, Folder 34)
  - Correspondence, 1919, 1936, 1947, 1960, 1965 (Box 245, Folder 35)
  - Drawings, undated (Box 245, Folder 36)
  - Europe trip, 1914 (Box 245, Folder 37)
  - Freud, Sigmund, manuscripts, undated (Box 245, Folder 38 - 39)
  - The Great Globe Itself, book reviews and miscellaneous, 1946 (Box 245, Folder 40)
  - Joint Congressional Committee on Foreign Economic Cooperation (China), economic, 1948 (Box 245, Folder 41)
  - Journalism research materials, China, 1947 (Box 245, Folder 42 - 43)
  - Journalism research materials, Formosa, 1953 (Box 245, Folder 44)
  - Journalism research materials, India and Southeast Asia, 1951 (Box 245, Folder 45)
  - Journalism research materials, Indochina, 1947 (Box 245, Folder 46)
  - Legal, 1944 (Box 245, Folder 47)
  - Legion of Merit, 1947 (Box 245, Folder 48)
  - London Economic Conference, 1933 (Box 245, Folder 49)
  - Morgan et Cie., 1934-1936 (Box 245, Folder 50 - 51)
  - Nancy trip, undated (Box 245, Folder 52)
  - Narodny, Ivan. The Art of Robert Winthrop Chandler. [autographed by author], 1934 (Box 245, Folder 52a)
  - Pamphlets, New York urban planning, 1941 (Box 246, Folder 53)
  - Pamphlets, miscellaneous, 1962 (Box 246, Folder 54)
  - Pan American report, 1942 (Box 246, Folder 55 - 56)
  - Periodicals, miscellaneous, 1916 (Box 246, Folder 57)
  - Personal, miscellaneous, 1914, 1943 (Box 246, Folder 58)
  - Photographs, Anne Bullitt papers, undated (Box 246, Folder 59)
  - Photographs, France, [1938] (Box 246, Folder 60)
  - Photographs, miscellaneous, undated (Box 246, Folder 61)
  - Photographs, people, undated (Box 247, Folder 62 - 64)
  - Photographs, Philadelphia mayoral campaign, [1943] (Box 247, Folder 65)
  - Photographs, Soviet Union, undated (Box 247, Folder 66)
  - Photographs, Tokyo, [ca 1956] (Box 247, Folder 67)
  - Posters, 1944 (Box 247, Folder 68)
  - Printed matter, miscellaneous, 1941 (Box 247, Folder 69)
  - Reference, 1946 (Box 247, Folder 70)
  - So Close to Greatness, undated (Box 247, Folder 71)
  - Spain trip, Anne Bullitt papers, 1948 (Box 247, Folder 72)
  - Speeches, articles, and notes, undated (Box 247, Folder 73)
  - Thomas Woodrow Wilson, publishing [royalties statements], 1967-1968 (Box 247, Folder 74)
  - Unidentified manuscripts, undated (Box 247, Folder 75)
  - Ambassador to the USSR, personnel, undated (Box 248, Folder 76)
  - Bullitt, Anne papers, 1968 (Box 248, Folder 77)
  - Joint Congressional Committee for Foreign Economic Cooperation (China), military, 1948 (Box 248, Folder 78)
  - Journalism research materials, China, 1947 (Box 248, Folder 79)
  - Legal, 1916 (Box 248, Folder 80)
  - Paris Peace Conference, Berne Conference, 1919 (Box 248, Folder 81)
  - Paris Peace Conference, world economic situation, 1919 (Box 248, Folder 82)
  - Thomas Woodrow Wilson, publishing [galleys], Circa 1966 (Box 248, Folder 83-84)
  - Bullitt, Anne papers, undated (Box 249B)
  - Chateau de St. Firmin, 1937 (Box 249A)
  - China and Manchuria, maps of, 1947 (Box 249C)
  - Chinese communists, scrapbook on, 1947 (Box 249D)
  - Correspondence, 1941, undated (Box 249E)
  - Free French Armed Forces, 1945 (Box 249F)
  - Joint Congressional Committee on Foreign Economic Cooperation (China), Congressional report, 1948 (Box 249G)
  - Joint Congressional Committee on Foreign Economic Cooperation (China), economic, 1948 (Box 249H)
  - Joint Congressional Committee on Foreign Economic Cooperation (China), miscellaneous, 1948 (Box 249I)
  - Journalism research materials, China, 1947 (Box 249J)
  - Kaoshiung House [blueprints], undated (Box 249K)
  - Maps and blueprints, general, 1914, 1932-1941, undated (Box 249L)
  - Paris Peace Conference maps and charts, 1919 (Box 249M)
  - Philadelphia mayoral campaign, post-war reconstruction, 1943 (Box 249N)
  - Reference [Taiwan map], undated (Box 249O)
  - Russia map, 1919 (Box 249P)
  - Maps, posters, and blueprints, 1919, 1936, 1945, 1948, undated (Box 250)
- Additional materials, Accession 2008-M-037
  Includes Accessions 2009-M-029 and 2009-M-033 (in Box 2). Accessions include correspondence, mainly to Anne Bullitt; presentation copy of Anne Morrow Lindbergh's Listen! the Wind inscribed by both Charles and Anne Lindbergh to Ambassador Bullitt; reports concerning indebtedness of European governments to the United States, circa 1932; materials relating to Anne Bullitt's marriage to and divorce from Daniel Brewster; and typescripts of Thomas Woodrow Wilson, a psychological study by Sigmund Freud and William Bullitt with related materials and photographs.
  - Bullitt, Anne Moen
    - Correspondence
      - Allen, Joan, circa 1930s (Box 1, Folder 1)
      - Baird, Emilie, Undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
      - Bryant, Louise, 1929-1932 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      - Bullitt, Lucy and Orville Bullitt, Undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
      - Bullitt, Ray, 1933-1935 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      - Bullitt, William C., Circa 1929-1935 (Box 1, Folder 6)
      - Chappell, F. V., 1930 (Box 1, Folder 7)
      - Eipper, Margaret, Undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
      - Fitzgerald, Mary, Undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
      - Frankel, Martha Ellen, Undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
      - Horter, Elizabeth, 1934-1936 (Box 1, Folder 11)
      - Incomplete names, circa 1930s (Box 1, Folder 12)
      - Ingersoll, Rita D., Undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
      - Ismail, Refik, 1929-1930 (Box 1, Folder 14)
      - K, Undated (Box 1, Folder 15)
      - Kent, Kathleen W., 1935-1936 (Box 1, Folder 16)
      - Martin, Harriet E., Undated (Box 1, Folder 17)
      - Mijoin, Louise, 1934 (Box 1, Folder 18)
      - Minot, Anna Lodge, Undated (Box 1, Folder 19)
      - Morlock, George A., 1934 (Box 1, Folder 20)
      - Offie, Carmel, Undated (Box 1, Folder 21)
      - P, 1934 (Box 1, Folder 22)
      - R, Undated (Box 1, Folder 23)
      - Schoedler, Lillian (Filene), 1936 (Box 1, Folder 24)
      - Thomson, Mr. and Mrs. Frank Graham, Undated (Box 1, Folder 25)
      - Walker, Norman, Undated (Box 1, Folder 26)
      - Wasserman, Marie, Undated (Box 1, Folder 27)
      - Unsent holiday cards and postcards, Undated (Box 1, Folder 28-29)
    - Artwork, Circa 1930s (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Schoolwork, 1931-1936 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Miscellaneous papers, Circa 1935 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Bullitt, William C.
    - Correspondence
      - B, 1931 (Box 1, Folder 33)
      - Baruch, Bernard, 1932 (Box 1, Folder 34)
      - Blackburn, Katherine, Undated (Box 1, Folder 35)
      - Bullitt, Orville, 1931-1932 (Box 1, Folder 36)
      - Burkinshaw, Neil, 1931-1932 (Box 1, Folder 37)
      - C, 1931-1932 (Box 1, Folder 38)
      - Chang Ming-kai, 1956-1958 (Box 1, Folder 39)
      - Dorel, G., 1931 (Box 1, Folder 40)
      - F, Circa 1931-1932 (Box 1, Folder 41)
      - Freud, Sigmund, 1932 (Box 1, Folder 42)
      - G, 1931-1932 (Box 1, Folder 43)
      - Girard Trust Co., 1931-1932 (Box 1, Folder 44-45)
      - Guffy, Joseph, 1932 (Box 1, Folder 46)
      - H, 1932 (Box 1, Folder 47)
      - Hahn, Kurt, 1932 (Box 1, Folder 48)
      - Hays, Arthur G., 1928 (Box 1, Folder 49)
      - House, Edward M., 1931-1932 (Box 1, Folder 50)
      - Incomplete names, 1932 (Box 1, Folder 51)
      - J-L, 1932-1933 (Box 1, Folder 52)
      - McCallum, George B., Undated (Box 1, Folder 53)
      - N, 1931 (Box 1, Folder 54)
      - O, 1932 (Box 1, Folder 55)
      - O'Donnell, John, 1932 (Box 1, Folder 56)
      - Packard, A. G., 1932 (Box 1, Folder 57)
      - Platt, Yungman & Co., 1932 (Box 1, Folder 58)
      - R, Circa 1931 (Box 1, Folder 59)
      - Roosevelt, Franklin, 1932 (Box 1, Folder 60)
      - S, Circa 1931-1932 (Box 1, Folder 61)
      - Seymour, Charles, 1932 (Box 1, Folder 62)
      - Shoop, Max, 1931 (Box 1, Folder 63)
      - Walker, Frank, 1932 (Box 1, Folder 64)
      - Wehle, Louis B., 1932 (Box 1, Folder 65)
      - White, Perry, Schnader & Maris, 1931 (Box 1, Folder 66)
      - Wilson, Woodrow, 1916-1919 (Box 1, Folder 67)
    - Diplomatic and Public Service Papers
      - Political memoranda, Circa 1932 (Box 1, Folder 68)
      - Travel documents, 1931-1935 (Box 1, Folder 69)
      - Itineraries and travel arrangements, Circa 1930s (Box 1, Folder 70)
      - Staff at Spaso-House (Russian Embassy), Circa 1934 (Box 1, Folder 71)
    - Writings
      - Speech on foreign affairs, Circa 1932 (Box 1, Folder 72)
    - Photographs, Circa 1930s (Box 1, Folder 73)
    - Printed matter
      - Lindbergh, Anne Morrow, Listen! The Wind, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 74)
  - Bullitt, Anne Moen
    - Brewster, Daniel
      - Correspondence
        - Circa 1968-1975 (Box 2, Folder 1)
        - Concerning divorce, Circa 1971 (Box 2, Folder 2)
        - Concerning laws in Connecticut and Maryland for involuntary commitment of an individual, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 3)
        - Newsclippings and documents on his bribery arrest and trial, 1969-1975 (Box 2, Folder 4)
        - Photographs, Circa 1970 (Box 2, Folder 5)
        - Rough drafts and press announcement of his speech to National Student Association, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Clippings and correspondence, 1967-1971 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence from Irish President Sean T. O'Kelly and Mrs. Phyllis O'Kelly, 1956-1966 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Bullitt, William C.
    - Correspondence from Sean T. O'Kelly, President of Ireland, 1957 February 1 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Thomas Woodrow Wilson, Twenty-eighth President of the United States: A Psychological Study, by Sigmund Freud and William C. Bullitt
      - Typescript from presentation binder, 1941 (Box 2, Folder 10-12)
      - Annotated typescript, original, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 13-15)
      - Annotated typescript, carbon copy, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 16-18)
      - Documents concerning rights and publication, 1956-1995 (Box 2, Folder 19)
      - Presentation case, 1941 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Photographs, Undated (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Additional materials, 1934-1958; Accession 2009-M-051
  Includes Accession 2009-M-057.
  - Letter and report by Garfield C. Burke to William Bullitt regarding formulation of a World Union, Circa 1940-1959 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Monetary and Economic Conference at Guild Hall, London, invitation, 1933 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Photograph of Ambassador Bullitt in his Moscow office, 1934 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Bullitt family tree, Undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Honorary diplomas and awards, 1934-1958 (Box 2)
  - Ambassador William C. Bullitt, NBC broadcast [commercially-produced], 1940 August 18; 2 phonograph records (33.3 rpm) (Box 4)
    - Preservation master, 3
      Contact Public Services (phone: 203 432-1735, e-mail: mssa.reference@yale.edu) for information on accessing this digital object.
      - Use copy, tracks 1-3, compact disc (Audio CD) (Box 3.1U)
  - Inn. Pavilion American, William Bullitt, Paris, 1937 July 4; 2 phonograph records (63 rpm) (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Preservation master, 2
      - Use copy, tracks 4-5, 1 compact disc (Audio CD) (Box 3.1U)